myschoolapps.com 2018-05-10

# MySchoolApps - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Commitment

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this Privacy Policy, which explains the Heartland School Solutions practices and procedures regarding online information and the choices available to you concerning how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information that you provide us through our web site, www.myschoolapps.com.

## The Information We Collect

When you apply for benefits at the Site, Heartland School Solutions collects certain personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information is information that is not otherwise publicly available and may include such things as your first and last name, your physical address, including house number, street, city, state, and zip code, your e-mail address, your home and/or work phone number, your social security number, and certain income information.

## How We Use Your Information

Heartland School Solutions does not sell or exchange personally identifiable information with any third party other than the appropriate school district, and then only as necessary for business purposes. However, Heartland School Solutions may disclose personally identifiable information in response to law enforcement activity, to enforce its contracts or property rights, or when required by law.

## Data Security

Heartland School Solutions will use commercially reasonable means to protect the integrity of its Site and the confidentiality of the personally identifiable information that you provide. While we consider online security a priority, we cannot provide absolute assurances against, and will not be liable for, any breaches of confidentiality due to system failures or unauthorized access by third parties.

## Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to Heartland School Solutions. Heartland School Solutions is committed to following all the guidelines outlined in Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

Heartland School Solutions reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. When modified, Heartland School Solutions will post the revised version of the Privacy Policy on the Site. Any information collected will be used in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. Please check the Privacy Policy regularly to review any changes. 

Start Your Online Application
